[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What role in the movie Dirty Dancing was the first to be cast?", "correct_answer": "Penny", "incorrect_answers": ["Baby", "Dr. Houseman (Babys Dad)", "Johnny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals are raining from the sky at the end of the 1999 drama movie Magnolia?", "correct_answer": "Frogs", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish", "Mice", "Cats and dogs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2003 independent film, directed by Jim Jarmusch, consists of eleven short stories, which focus on coffee and cigarettes.", "correct_answer": "Coffee and Cigarettes", "incorrect_answers": ["Buttermilk and Cigarettes", "200 Cigarettes and Black Coffee", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Western games is most similar to Mahjong?", "correct_answer": "Rummy", "incorrect_answers": ["Bridge", "Dominoes", "Risk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the villains evil henchwoman in The Spy Who Loved Me, who chases James Bond in a helicopter?", "correct_answer": "Naomi", "incorrect_answers": ["Gayle", "Euridice", "Zelda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to a study published in the Annals of Neurology, people who regularly come into contact with pesticides are 70 % more likely to develop what disease?", "correct_answer": "Parkinsons disease", "incorrect_answers": ["Brain Cancer", "Alzheimers disease", "Jakob-Brezlov disease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Aye-aye character from the 2005 animated comedy movie Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Maurice", "incorrect_answers": ["Marty", "Mort", "King Julien"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the real name of the American female artist known as Pink?", "correct_answer": "Alecia", "incorrect_answers": ["Pamella", "Emily", "Stacey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which animal has the longest gestation period?", "correct_answer": "Black Salamander", "incorrect_answers": ["Polar Bear", "Dung Beetle", "Sumatran Rhino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Norman Breakey invent?", "correct_answer": "The paint roller", "incorrect_answers": ["The electric alarm clock", "The electric typewriter", "The QWERTYU keyboard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Calculate 6!", "correct_answer": "720", "incorrect_answers": ["36", "21", "216"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Hindu thought, how was Krishna killed?", "correct_answer": "By an arrow into his heel", "incorrect_answers": ["By poisoning by Shiva", "By the abominations of mankind", "By a knife into his heart"]}]